asdonline.com 2013-04-20

# 

**Effective Date: January 2011**

## Privacy Notice

This privacy notice covers the collection and use of information for this website, (“this website”). This website is managed and operated by Nielsen to promote the ASD Shows. As the producer of the nations largest merchandise trade shows, Nielsen Exposition's Merchandise Group, ASD provides a portfolio of innovative face-to-face, print, and online products for the wholesale trade industry. Founded in 1961, ASD continues to develop new solutions to provide Buyers and Sellers the most comprehensive marketplace in today's dynamic retail environment. ASD's product portfolio connects sellers from manufacturing to wholesale distribution with buyers from independent retailers to international chain stores. Nielsen Business Media is part of The Nielsen Company, a global information and media company. 

## About Nielsen

Nielsen is a global information and media company with leading market positions in marketing and consumer information, television and other media measurement, online intelligence, mobile measurement, trade shows and business publications. The privately held company is active in approximately 100 countries, with headquarters in New York, USA. For more information please visit [www.nielsen.com](http://www.nielsen.com/). Nielsen owns and operates multiple trade shows, publications, conferences and websites serving various industries and has operated ASD since 1961. 

## What information we collect and how we use it

We collect personally identifiable information that you choose to provide to us when you register for a trade show, subscribe to our magazines (either directly or through another company such as a subscription agency), sign up for email newsletters, enter a contest, or participate in surveys. During the registration process we may request certain contact information and demographic information about you such as name, mailing address, email address, company name, size of company and title. We do not sell or share this information with third parties, except as described below. We also may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us. If you choose to register for a trade show on this website, you may also be asked to provide your credit card information to fulfill your registration request. 

## When we may disclose your information to others

Nielsen may use your contact information for any of the following reasons:

  * To provide you with information about products or services you've ordered, including trade shows. 
  * To provide you with e-newsletters you have requested 
  * To send you notices for subscription renewal 
  * To contact you regarding marketing endeavors 

If you do not wish to receive ASD marketing information from Nielsen or wish to opt out of future ASD email promotions from Nielsen, please email [nielsenexpositionsprivacy@nielsen.com](mailto:%20nielsenexpositionsprivacy@nielsen.com) with ASD in the subject line. Please note that all promotional and research email messages you receive from Nielsen will include an option to opt out of future email communications. 

From time to time Nielsen may also share your contact information with other organizations, such as trade show exhibitors and vendors, for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please [click here](http://o.nielsen-info.com/no.aspx). 

We contract with third party companies that we have employed to provide us with specialized services, including customer service, registration, subscription fulfillment, housing, research, statistical analysis, list cleansing, postal mailings, email and fax deployment, and other information services. These companies or individuals may be provided with access to personally identifiable information, but only as needed to perform their functions. These companies are required by contract to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of such information. 

Notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy notice, we may disclose personally identifiable information to any third party when disclosure is required by law, or desirable to permit us to exercise or preserve our legal rights or take action regarding potentially illegal activities or to protect the safety of any person. In the event we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity or in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

## Cookies and Web beacons

We may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files a site uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to the site and facilitate the use of the site. "Cookies" also allow a site to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising. 

We may also use third-party advertising companies such as Google to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (i.e. not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements on this website and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

## Children

This site is not directed at children under the age of 13 and does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that this website has collected the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact [nielsenexpositionsprivacy](mailto:%20nielsenexpositionsprivacy@nielsen.com). 

## Data storage, transfers and security

We may store the personal details we hold about you for as long as needed, which may be indefinitely. We may store this information in the United States or we may transfer it to any other country. The data protection laws in countries to which personal data are transferred may or may not provide a level of protection equivalent to the laws in your home country. Wherever we hold the data, we will apply the terms of this privacy notice and any applicable data protection law. We maintain certain procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of personally identifiable information while it is controlled by us. However, the storage and communication of personal data cannot always be completely secure. Also, we cannot and do not guarantee that data transferred to third parties in accordance with this privacy notice will be protected against intentional or accidental misuse or loss. Please contact us if you have questions or wish to take any action with respect to information to which this privacy notice applies. You can reach us by sending an email to [nielsenexpositionsprivacy@nielsen.com](mailto:%20nielsenexpositionsprivacy@nielsen.com). 

We may change this privacy notice and our data collection and management practices. We reserve the right to update changes to this privacy notice and to our practices in collecting and handling personally identifiable information. If we make material changes, we will notify you by email prior to their implementation and let you decide if you want the material changes to apply to your personally-identifiable information. We will also post a prominent notice at this website and indicate at the top of this statement when it was most recently updated.
